What was your team hoping
to find here in Pompeii?
I'll never tell a scum like you.
That's so. What a shame.
But they're still your two friends.
I'm sure one of them could be
persuaded into spilling their guts.
Which makes you WORTHLESS!
Those footsteps.
Someone's running around
outside the mirror.
Well now, would you look at that?
Could it be your friends dumped you in favor
of pursuing their precious secret item?
The trail of sound is heading
towards the Kaveh Kanam.
There's no question.
Killing you isn't worth the
effort it'd take to do it.
I think I'll go snatch whatever
it is you're so keen on finding!
No!
You're not going anywhere!
Abakio! Giorno!
Where is it?
Where's the key?
Aha, gotcha.
Huh?
A mirror?
It's not from around here.
What's that you got there?
A key?
Heavens me!
This is gonna be like taking
candy from a washed-up baby!
You see?
What now?
Try as you might, you can't unsee me!
The die has been cast
and your fate is sealed!
Let's go.
I'll see you
next
time.
Oh, shit, not good!
I'm starting to understand how this
Katsune messes with people's heads.
So he's hiding inside the mirror.
And logically speaking, that
can only mean one thing.
That reflective reject must have
dragged Fugo into a mirror world,
effectively separating him from his stand.
It's a shame, but the key comes first!
Your breaking the mirror just
made my job that much easier.
Reflections act as portals
to the mirror world.
By breaking it into pieces, you practically
handed me your life on a silver platter.
I shall grant you exclusive access to
my world, but only your physical self.
Gotcha now.
You're gonna be stuck in here for life.
But first, I'll be taking that key.
How the hell are you?
Y-you can only do this
with the power of a stand!
I dragged you in here alone!
There's no way you can
be choking Mirror Man!
Guess breaking that mirror
wasn't such a mistake after all.
Your view of the outside world
just got a whole lot narrower.
You did drag something in here.
Problem is, you can't see!
You gave me access.
But just for my physical self?!
Wait, is that...
Thanks for making my job easier.
Moody Jazz!
I pulled in his stand!
Inside the mirror,
everything is ass backwards.
It's almost impossible to
figure out that trick until
the bastard decides to
attack you with his stand.
Fugo must be somewhere in here too.
But how the hell do we
get out of this place?
If I have to massacre your
ass to escape, then so be it!
You're about to get a first-hand look at
why I sent Moody Jazz
into your mirror prison!
So your power is an anthropomorphic
shape-shifting stand.
Well done, Stronto. You got me.
You know, when all is said and done, your
wimpy little stand is pretty damn feeble.
You're screwed unless you're
fighting a total weakling.
Well, come on, let's get this over with.
Hey, didn't I already tell you?
You're as good as dead,
my long-haired friend.
You managed to startle me slightly
when you showed up with a stand,
but you're still a goner.
Did it occur to you that
I'm crouching for a reason?
I'm doing it because I
have no other choice!
Obviously.
You're hunched over to give my
foot a clear path to your gut.
Actually, I was crouching so I
could pick up this shard of mirror.
Hey, what's with the bewildered face?
Does this arm scare you?
I think you of all people
would recognize it.
I told you from the beginning, reflections
serve as portals to another world.
By using a piece of glass to capture your
reflection, I created another portal.
Do you get it?
I dragged something special
into this mirror world.
Your stinking arm!
We wouldn't want you to get too excited.
So only half your body was
allowed into this world.
As for your stand here, I'll be
nice and let half of it leave.
I've got you and your stand
exactly where I want you.
That key is mine.
Shit.
All that work and there goes the key.
That means not only did
I botch the mission,
but everything Giorno predicted
is about to come true.
I'm not leaving.
Trust me on this.
Finding Fugo and taking this guy down will
be our best shot at solving this mystery.
I might be down right now, but
I still have my pride, damn it.
He's not getting that damn key.
I swear on all that's holy.
I, Leone Abacchio, will
never give up this key.
Since Mirror Man focuses on dragging
fools like you into the Netherrealm,
it doesn't have much in the way of brute
force, but I'm well aware of its strengths.
For instance,
in a compromising position such as this,
it doesn't need the power of a superhuman
to finish off the likes of you!
In fact,
a four-year-old could slide this shard
down your gullet without breaking a sweat.
Ah, sweet victory!
Thanks for showing me exactly
where to find s - huh?
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and do it!
Explain yourself, Abakio.
You really think you can hide it from me?
Even if you can move your body, you
won't be able to escape me, you know.
I can see right through
you. Got that? Hide what?
What the hell are you talking about?
You're not making the least bit of sense.
Your bad acting isn't fooling anyone.
Now, show me your hand!
How are you doing this,
you freaking bastardo?
What, did you lose something?
Why so quiet?
I asked a question. Well?
Why would he do something like that?
Shit.
If this fool really chopped off his hand,
then the stand's hand that's
outside the mirror is...
It can't be.
The hand's gone.
His area.
No, it has the key.
And it's going back damn it the key
is getting away and that new recruit?
Giorno is just around the
corner he cut off his own hand
just to give him the key
should have killed me with that
piece of glass back when you
had a chance had you just done
that my stand's hand would have
dropped dead in its tracks?
Close but no cigar!
Too bad this is the sound of
your dreams disintegrating.
You'll pick up that key any second now!
Shape-shifting bastardo did you really
think i'd let that brat Giorno off the hook?
I'll just drag his ass
in here too so Giorno
do you finally get what
it's all about now?
As long as one of us gets
back with the key we're good.
Even if the one who does is
a piece of shit like you.
The only thing that matters is
successfully carrying out the mission.
Wow your thoughts are so loud I
can practically hear them Abakio?
Do you actually believe you know
what's going on outside the mirror?
If nothing else at least you have a loyal
partner it's a shame he's
not the brightest bulb.
He's throwing away all your hard work but
don't take my word for
it look for yourself.
The fool's not even attempting to
flee with the key seems he's decided
to stay put i suppose the But the
stress of the mission got to him!
Giorno!
What are you doing?
Move your ass!
You have the key!
Get out of there now!
You can scream until
you're even more purple.
He'll never hear you.
Is this really happening?
I now have two options at my disposal.
I could secure the key, then finish
off Giorno while basking in my victory.
Or I could lacerate his
trachea and major arteries,
watch him bleed out, then
collect the key at my leisure.
Now, what to do?
I think it's the perfect day for
slicing open this pug's throat!
Oh, he noticed me!
I guess I'll let him in,
but only his physical self.
Welcome to my world!
Slice away, Mirror Man!
Wh-what?!
No way, that's impossible!
It's the virus!
Damn that Giorno to hell!
He got himself infected
by Fugo's purple smoke!
The key stays with me, asshat.
And mark my words, before I'm done,
I'll bring back Fugo and
Abbacchio safe and south!
Damn that Giorno Giovanna.
He's an arrogant, ignorant prick.
Purple smoke will turn him into
human fertilizer before he knows it.
I'll never forget part of me
died on that horrible day.
It left me completely numb.
The thought of losing a limb
doesn't scare me in the least.
The only thing that brings
me solace now is carrying
out the orders of an
omnipotent and powerful leader.
Devoting myself to this mission has
given my miserable life new purpose.
Put simply, my orders were to
retrieve the key and protect the girl.
Completing the mission
meant everything to me.
And yet Giorno,
the Chiricolione,
instead of getting the key back safely,
he decided to risk the whole
plan to save me and Fugo.
Stupid brat, how dare you bring
that filthy disease in here?
Are you out of your mind?
You Goldilocks goon, you infected me!
Ah, you have the same nasty symptoms I do.
It takes about 30 seconds for Purple
Smoke's virus to infect the entire body.
Your life is over now.
The writing was already
on the wall when you
decided to pull me into your mirror world.
The mirror that Purple
Smoke smashed to pieces.
Giorno fixed some shards when
the enemy chased after Abbacchio.
He took some shards with him.
Giorno must have realized that.
That's how he figured out
the enemy's abilities.
He infected himself with the virus,
then allowed himself to be
dragged into the mirror.
There was no other way to take
down a killer this cunning.
This can't be happening.
Damn you to hell, Stronto.
Idiot.
Don't celebrate just yet.
I haven't been beaten.
I just need to steal myself
for the end of this battle.
Now, mere man, allow me
to leave this hellhole.
Me and only me.
However, keep that damn virus contained!
No part of my body contaminated
with the virus, so leave!
Merda, he's going to isolate the
virus inside the mirror world with us!
If that cocky kagagatso can cut off
his own damn hand to get the key,
then you can bet your ass that
I'm willing to do the same thing!
Oh, the glorious pain!
Giorno, grab him before he gets away!
He's gone.
Giorno, he slipped through our fingers.
You risked your life to
come in here, and for what?
If he's gone, so's the mirror world.
Almost got me there.
But the joke's on you, assholes.
The key to success is mental fortitude.
This is simply a setback.
I had a hunch he'd leave his mirror world.
Though all hope isn't lost yet.
He doesn't know it, but his
fate was sealed a while back.
By stepping outside his
little mirror dimension,
he may have inadvertently
saved my life. Fugo!
Now that he's outside the mirror world,
Purple Smoke will be able to follow him!
Finish him off!
I'm sorry, Giorno.
I really wish I could, but I can't
tell where he is from inside here.
I have no way to attack him! I'm useless!
I know exactly where he is. Earlier,
Golden Wind took the liberty of transforming
that brick outside into a snake.
That's why it's moving.
Snakes can detect infrared radiation
from warm bodies, human bodies included.
Got him!
What?
After all that mental preparation to
chop off my own arm and leave my realm?
This can't be!
Stop it!
I said stop it, damn you!
No, one hit from the death
virus capsule and I'm a goner!
Looks like lady luck
hasn't abandoned me yet.
If mirror man can just catch his
punch for a fraction of a second,
I might have a chance.
I just need to block it once.
Finish him off now. Purple smoke.
End this. Mirror man.
This invalid needs to die now.
I...
I did it!
I stopped it!
Now to take this back with me
into my lethal looking glass!
What?
But how?
I blocked its punch!
It didn't strike anything!
I was physically and mentally prepared
to plunge myself into the real world!
we did it we broke out of the mirror
house from hell we finished him
and took care of his stand in the
process giorno you've been infected
purple smoke is in your blood it's
circulating throughout your whole body
once you've been infected there's
nothing i can do yeah i know that but
everything worked out for the best
trust me him leaving his house of
mirrors really turned the tide in our
favor pulling my diseased body into
the mirror was well the proverbial
nail in the coffin who would have
thought the guy's refusal to admit defeat
would turn out to be my lucky break
fortunately he recalled
his powers just before
i was about to die
bringing me face to face
with this friendly snake
that snake the cloud
of purple smoke's virus
doesn't phase it at all
that's right i created this
snake from a brick immersed
in purple smoke's viral vapor
the virus was a part of his
natural habitat so he came
into the world disease-free
do you get what i'm saying now
amigo yes that's brilliant it
was born with an immunity
since it has natural defenses
if we harvest its blood and
cells we can make an antivirus
and stop the disease let's get
to work golden wind extract
the antiviral serum from this
snake and Injected to my body!
Giorno Giovanna.
When I first met him, I
thought he was just an oddball.
with his head in the clouds.
But he comes up with the
most harebrained ideas?
And somehow actually manages.
to find a way to pull them off.
There's something about him that I trust.
He has an authenticity
you can't put into words.
You sprang into action,
just like Bucciarati.
Giorno, you went above
and beyond to save us.
You have my eternal respect.
No, Fugo.
I did my part, but I'm not
the one who missed his life.
I simply made a prediction
and acted accordingly.
The one who truly risked
his life was Abakio.
He sustained serious injuries back there.
You should have seen him.
He risked everything for that key.
If he hadn't successfully delivered
the key, we wouldn't be here right now.
We would have been demolished.
Don't worry about me.
He needs urgent help. Giorno!
Giorno!
Are you okay?
Damn it, Giorno!
I was going to beat the
ever-living shit out of you.
But with my hand like
this, I guess I can't.
For now, I guess your
ass-kicking will have to wait.
In the end, the team got their key.
Every time I close my eyes.
Wake up feeling so horny!
I can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see?
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me!
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaky, you is all I need!
I need your body.
Tonight, you got my time.
I'll give it to you, baby!
Tonight, you won't be sorry.
Tonight,
you got my mind.
If you've got my mind, all
I want to do is free to you.
What must I say?
Tell me.
What must I do?
To show how much I'm going to free to you.
What must I say?
What must I do?
To show how much I'm going to free to you.
I'm gonna break it all.
Thank you.